<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
   <name>Impacts</name>
   <key>impacts</key>
   <state>stable</state>
   <logo>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tomolimo/impacts/master/impacts.png</logo>
   <description>
      <short>
		   <fr>Migre les données des versions précédentes du plugin dans les tables du coeur de GLPI 9.5 et permet d'ajouter des types pour les analyses d'impacts. </fr>
         <en>Migrates former version plugin data into GLPÏ 9.5 core tables and add possibility to add new types to impact analysis.</en>
      </short>
      <long>
         <en>This release migrates the data from the former version of this plugin into the GLPI 9.5 core tables. And provides possiblity to add any GLPI object types (or any plugin object types) into the list of enabled types for impact analysis. It gives also the possibility to change the icons for GLPI core item types (or for plugin item types).

*Icon credit: Network by priyanka from the Noun Project*</en>
		   <fr>Cette version du plugin migre les données des versions précédentes dans les table du coeur de GLPI 9.5. Et fournit la possibilité d'ajouter n'importe quel type d'objet GLPI (ou type d'objet d'un plugin) dans la liste des types activés pour l'analyse d'impact. Il donne aussi la possibilité de changeer les icônes des types du coeur de GLPI (ou bien des types des plugins).

*Icon credit: Network by priyanka from the Noun Project*</fr>
      </long>
   </description>
   <homepage>https://github.com/tomolimo/impacts</homepage>
   <download>https://github.com/tomolimo/impacts/releases</download>
   <issues>https://github.com/tomolimo/impacts/issues</issues>
   <readme>https://github.com/tomolimo/impacts/wiki</readme>
   <authors>
      <author>Olivier Moron</author>
   </authors>
   <versions>
      <version>
         <num>1.1.0</num>
         <compatibility>9.2</compatibility>
      </version>
      <version>
         <num>1.2.0</num>
         <compatibility>9.3</compatibility>
      </version>
      <version>
         <num>1.3.7</num>
         <compatibility>9.3</compatibility>
         <compatibility>9.4</compatibility>
      </version>
      <version>
         <num>2.0.3</num>
         <compatibility>9.5</compatibility>
      </version>
   </versions>
   <langs>
      <lang>en_gb</lang>
      <lang>fr_fr</lang>
   </langs>
   <license>GPL v2+</license>
   <tags>
      <fr>
         <tag>Inventaire</tag>
         <tag>Impact</tag>
         <tag>Lien</tag>
		   <tag>Relation</tag>
		   <tag>Graphe</tag>
      </fr>
      <en>
         <tag>Inventory</tag>
         <tag>Impact</tag>
         <tag>Link</tag>
		   <tag>Relation</tag>
		   <tag>Graph</tag>
      </en>
   </tags>
   <screenshots>
      <screenshot>https://github.com/tomolimo/impacts/raw/master/screenshots/graph.png</screenshot>
      <screenshot>https://github.com/tomolimo/impacts/raw/master/screenshots/form.png</screenshot>
   </screenshots>
</root>
